people being real audacious, okay? My ex before my ex got the nerve to come and comment on my page
like he wasn't an incredibly mean and terrible man to me. And I have a habit of looking with
incredibly mean and terrible men because I have daddy issues. Well, I'm over 40 now, so they're
father issues. And I'm constantly working on them joints. Nonetheless, this man has never paid me
back for bailing him out of jail, for holding him down when he was down. You know, I remember when
I had nothing. I mean, I clearly don't have no more of this, but I remember when I had nothing and now
I've got something. People be real bold, okay? Audacity should be the same as gas prices. This is a man
who, unbeknownst to me, took a picture of me while I was presenting him with an oral gift.
And then, months later, when he tried to cash a check that I did not clear to cash,
he then tried to extort me by saying, I will post this picture to the public unless you clear this
check. Mm-hmm. That person is on my page right now, commenting on my posts, following me. Mm-hmm.
No, I didn't clear the check because when you look at the picture, all it shows is that I've got skills
and flexibility. Anyways, to everybody out there who has loved somebody that I believe everybody
deserves love, but I don't believe that everybody should get the opportunity to receive what they
cannot reciprocate. So, to all my folks out there that have been in that situation,
on this Sunday, release it. Release them. Release yourself from the... Because I know I will beat myself
up like, ooh, you really got played. But ultimately, you know, when someone plays a good person, they end up
playing themselves. And that's really all it boils down to. But I do want my money. I do.
Because we have an agreement. Mm-hmm. And that is TRIPOLIN!